The last question you'd really appreciate.
Monday, we're about 7.22.
We're going to have an invitation about back to the winter.
Hear them.
Thank you, sir.
That's great.
Well, again, we are so grateful for seeing that you gave us the
joy of blessing.
We thank you, Father.
It's a timely limit.
We pray for our leaders.
We may elect.
We've got a who are called a sir.
And here are fours.
We thank our civil servants.
We do have a value of that.
We've got a leading us in taking good care.
So we've got a list of this down in this community.
We pray all these things.
And Jesus Christ's precious.
And help me in the new prayer.
Amen.
I pledge allegiance to the flag of the United States of America.
And as you say, we are about to look for which it stands.
One nation under God in the visible liberty and justice for all.
More to give us a fifth and more to the present.
Hi.
He's in the dentist.
That's going to be a group of six and seven.
So move.
Second.
Davis.
Hi.
A step.
I.
Parker.
Hi.
You know, Mr. Avenue.
They just write the name.
Please.
For your day.
So Mr. Mayor.
And.
Council members.
So.
This contract is persuade to discussion.
For the exact session on January 18.
We are.
We move forward for that discussion.
We're legal.
Action related to the.
We are.
They're licensing.
The.
You.
Those.
Would.
Said.
bar Dutch.
A.
Mix.
We will need.
Cure.
Second.
I.
The.
Cities.
I.
There.
The Council have approved the contract with the building and the services.
Today, we're just circling back with the emission rate.
It also has to approve the same contract.
Again, this contract is for a claim, and you can assure the city rates,
we're sent appropriate to recover on our costs.
Thank you.
I
My
Parker
Yeah, I was in this being a